in just a couple of seconds more than
half of Hiroshima had been eviscerated
and some 880,000 civilians had perished
many more would die in the following
days weeks and years as severe burns
under the harmful effects of radiation
began to take its toll following the
bombing Truman would release a message
broadcasting a warning to Japan live for
the world to
hear if they do not now accept our terms
they may expect a reign of Ruin from the
air the like of which has never been
seen on this Earth behind this Air
Attack will follow sea and land forces
in such numbers and power as they have
not yet seen and with the fighting skill
of which they are already well
aware radio messages will also broadcast
to Japan every 15 minutes warning that
more cities would be targeted unless an
immediate surrender was received